Yash Pratap Singh Parmar

Yash66579@gmail.com

Chhatarpur, Madhya Pradesh

Phone: +91 9109219838

Linkdin, Naukri, Website

I am a Front-End Developer, having a total of 2-year Experience, 1 year of Progressive Experience in Operation Executive and 1 year of Experience in Freelancing, Energetic and easily adapt any situations. Navigates high-stress situations and achieve goals on time. Skills in establishing strong channels of Communication Between Team Members.

EDUCATION

Babulal Tarabai Institute of Research and Technology, Sagar, M.P

2018-2022

- CGPA: 7.8 / 10
- Relevant Coursework: B. TECH in Computer Science and Engineering

Work Experience

Buzz Sports Entertainment PVT.LTD, Gurugram, India

Operations Executive

Sept 2022 - Nov 2023

- Manages the Operations of different Sports Like cricket, football etc. Create a different Contests or Leagues according to the Users Demand.
- Analyse the user's data and makes a report on the daily, weekly and monthly basis.
- Also solve the customer issues and quarries.
- Also do Research work on Player's analytics, performance etc.
- Familiar in working with Power BI and Ms-Office.

Freelancing Web designer & Content Writer

March 2021 - Aug 2022

- Working with youtubers as a content writer and website Manager. Working in SEO, Keywords Research, Content Editor, Content Writer etc.
- Worked as a web-designer create and customize WordPress website on the user's demand.
- Working in a Bakery Shop Website as a Main Designer.

Additional Skills

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP
- Basic knowledge of JAVA SCRIPT, REACT.JS, PYTHON, DSA
- Basic knowledge of FIGMA
- Intermediate speaking level in English but Proficient in Hindi

Projects

- Portfolio Website, this is resume site a single page site and also this website is not fully responsive languages that I used is: - HTML, CSS, JS and BOOTSTRAP, Icons From Fontawsome. LINK
- Personal Website, this is my Personal resume site a single page Fully Responsive site languages that I used is: - HTML, CSS, JS, BOOTSTRAP, AOS ANIMATIONS, Icons from Icons8 and Fontawsome. LINK
- This is a Fully Responsive Login Page, languages that I used is: HTML, CSS. LINK
- Amazone Clone Website, It's a Home Page of Amazone Website this a WebView page of amazon making using only a HTML, CSS. <u>LINK</u>